Friends, have you also downloaded any PDF in your mobile phone?  If
you have a PDF of anything and want to know its password
, then how do we find the password of the PDF
?
In this video, we are going to tell you a very good method, we are going to
teach you how you will be able to find the password of a PDF
?  How to know if
PDF has a password?  I am going to
tell you and teach you a very good trick in this video.
So let's move
ahead in this video.  So hello and welcome
friends, you are watching Android Junction
YouTube channel and my name is Rupesh.
Friends, let's start today's
video and yes friends, on this channel
we keep bringing such valuable content for you daily, so please
like the video and also subscribe to the channel,
let's move ahead friends,
how will you find the password of any PDF,
in this video we tell you,
teach you, give you all the information in detail about
how you will find the password of any PDF.
Actually what happens is that when we
open any PDF here,
it is not protected with a password as it is kept for privacy, so if
we do not have the password here,
we are not able to know what the password of the PDF is.
People have already told many methods here
on YouTube and everywhere else to tell this, but it might
not be working here, you also know this
and you might also be worried.
Whatever method I will tell you here, I will tell you genuine which is
working.  Let us tell you the complete process.  For example, whatever
file you have here will have its name.
Ok?  For example, suppose you have a
State Bank of India statement and
need its password or you have an Airtel call
history and need its password.  If
you need any kind of password, then go
to the Chrome browser of your mobile phone.
Like we have Airtel call
history.  Ok?  So from here I search
Airtel Call
History
PDF
Password
Format format, in this way if you have
SBI statement or whatever it is,
you will write it and search, write its name
like SBI Statement PDF
Password Format or whatever it is, write it in front,
after that write PDF Password
Format, after writing search,
as if you are searching, now see here
many things will be written here,
here you will get the complete format
of the password, what type of password is it,
okay, as you can see,
here it is being told that our
password is of Airtel, here how is the
password of call history.  So its format
is explained here.  You can view the password for
your Airtel call history PDF is a
combination of your SIM owner name and the
last four digits of your mobile number.  Ok
?  It is saying that owner's name and the
last four digits of your mobile number.
Specifically, it is useful that the first two letters
of the SIM owner's name are followed by the
four digits of your mobile number. For example,
the SIM owner's name and last four
digits are written as R1, 23, and J0. So,
here the format is given
as if our name will have two letters and the
last four letters of our SIM card.  The
password will be like this.  So
here I got the format.  If you
search like this, you will get the format.
See, now we are entering the same password here
and opening our PDF.  See if it is
happening or not.  Now I put it here.
After entering, click OK and you
can see that our PDF has opened.  So this
is the best way to find out the password of any PDF.
Come to Chrome browser and search from here,
you will get the format.  Other people
will tell us different methods but our work
cannot be done through them.  Finally, from here we get to
know the format of passwords etc. properly.
So we hope you enjoyed the video.  If you like it then please
support.  Like the video and
subscribe to the channel friends.  See you
in another video.  Till then, you all take
good care of yourselves.  Bye bye
friends.